(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
1st 兎田ぺこらいぶ「うさぎ the MEGAMI!!」
受注販売グッズ
1st Pekora Live 'Usagi the MEGAMI!!'
Merchandise for Sale
野うさぎペンライト / 野うさぎタオル / Tシャツ
Wild Rabbit Penlight / Wild Rabbit Towel / T-shirt
ステンドグラス風キーホルダー / ブレスレット / ブックカバー
Stained Glass-style Keychain / Bracelet / Book Cover
アクリルスタンド / クリアファイル＆缶バッジセット / タペストリー
Acrylic Stand / Clear File & Can Badge Set / Tapestry
うさぎ the MEGAMI!!
Usagi the MEGAMI!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
公演ハッシュタグ #うさめかぺこら
Performance Hashtag #UsamekaPekora
応援セット 受注販売
Support Set (Order Sale)
うさぎ the MEGAMI!!
Usagi the MEGAMI!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show starts
公演ハッシュタグ #うさめがぺこら
Concert Hashtag #UsamegaPekora
みなさーん！こんぺこー！
Everyone! Konpeko!
兎田ぺこらでーす！
I'm Usada Pekora!
今日は楽しんでいこうねー！
Let's have fun today!
それじゃあ、いくよー！
Alright, here we go!
せーの！
One, two!
1st 兎田ぺこらいぶ「うさぎ the MEGAMI!!」にご来場いただき、ありぺこー！
1st Usada Pekora Live 'Usagi the MEGAMI!!' Thank you for coming, Ari-peko!
こんぺこ！こんぺこ！こんぺこ！ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらぺこー！どうも、どうも！
Kon-peko! Kon-peko! Kon-peko! Hololive 3rd Gen Usada Pekora-peko! Hello, hello!
ねぇ、あんたたちさ、すげぇ笑顔でカメラから切り抜かれてんじゃん。ぺこらもなんか、ニコニコしちゃったよ。さすがに、あんたたち、いーい感じで切り抜かれてんのを見て。
Hey, you guys have such great smiles being captured on camera. Peko-ra couldn't help but smile too, seeing you all captured in such a great way.
そんなね、みんなに最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかぺこらからご案内させていただくぺこ。
To make sure everyone enjoys the live until the end, Peko-ra has a few announcements to make-peko.
ハハッ！いいや、声出てるねー！今日頼むぞ、マジで！
Haha! Wow, your voices are coming out well! I'm counting on you today, seriously!
じゃあ行くね。公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたしております。
Okay, here I go. Photography, recording, and the use of filming equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
また、本公演は避難誘導灯の消灯を行います。
Also, the emergency exit lights will be turned off during this performance.
万が一、避難が必要になった場合は、すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、スタッフの指示に従ってください。
In the unlikely event that an evacuation becomes necessary, the emergency lights will be turned on immediately, so please follow the staff's instructions.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまったときは、無理はせずスタッフへ知らせてほしいぺこ。
If you should feel unwell, please don't push yourself and let the staff know-peko.
会場内でのモッシュ・ダイブ・肩車・ステージ上に物を投げ込む・ステージ上に上がる・奇声を上げる・前に押し寄せるなどの過激な応援行為、過度なジャンプ行為などは、
Mosh, diving, shoulder-riding, throwing things onto the stage, climbing onto the stage, shouting, pushing forward, and other excessive supporting behaviors, as well as excessive jumping...
他のみんなの迷惑になる公演を妨げる危険行為は、一切禁止です。
...and dangerous acts that disturb others and interfere with the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って、盛り上がってほしいぺこ。
Please follow the rules and let's get hyped-peko.
そして、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are in the venue, and the audience may be captured on film.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware in advance that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、#うさめがぺこら です。
Also, the hashtag for the live is #UsamegaPekora.
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさんたくさん盛り上げてほしいぺこ！
Use the hashtag and let's get hyped up more and more-peko!
なんか今のあんたたちの声だったら、もうしょっぱなから盛り上がれる気がするわ。
I feel like with those voices of yours, we can get hyped right from the start.
頼んだよ、あんたたち！
I'm counting on you guys!
それでは開演までもう少し！
Well then, just a little longer until the show starts!
みんな、盛り上がる準備できてるー！？
Is everyone ready to get hyped!?
ほんじゃライブでなー！またねー！
Well then, see you at the live! See ya!
PEKORA'S STORY
うさぎ the MEGAMI!!
Usagi the MEGAMI!!
START
旅立とう冒険
Let's set off on an adventure
そしてインドアの神話へ
And into the indoor mythos
最大級のラララララヴィ！
The greatest La-La-La-La-Love-it!
ピー！
Pee!
みんなー！ぺこらのハツライブへ来てくれて、
Everyone! Thanks for coming to Pekora's first live concert!
ありぺこー！
Aripeko!
いくぞー！有明アリーナ！
Here we go! Ariake Arena!
最序盤のスライムにビビるの解せない
I can't understand being scared of early-game slimes
オーマイラーイ
Oh my lie
1 2 3 で繋がった世界にアイ溢れ出す
In a world connected by 1, 2, 3, love overflows
エイトビットに感じるドキドキ
Feeling the excitement in 8-bit
通じぬラブじゃダメですか？
Is love that doesn't get through no good?
運ゲー？超絶？ふざけてんじゃねーぞ
Luck game? Super hard? Don't mess with me!
レベルアップして変えてやらあ
I'll level up and change it!
夢に見てるパーフェクトの音
The sound of the perfect I've dreamed of
落第・個性・土砂・凄・ロマンスの糧
Failure, individuality, debris, amazing—sustenance for romance
ラヴィラヴィ小さなビットにでっかい愛をパーシンチュウ
Love-it, Love-it, 100% of my big love in a tiny bit
ちょっと待っても許してね
Please forgive me even if I wait a bit
だって愛はひきこもり
Because love is a shut-in
ジャンピンジャンピン跳ねるハートをつかまえておいてね
Jumping, jumping, catch my bouncing heart and hold on to it
未踏なんて終わらないで
Don't let the unexplored end
ブルーエンドになるまで
Until it becomes a blue end
最大級のラララララヴィ！
The greatest La-La-La-La-Love-it!
ラヴィ！
Love-it!
ギルドかけて無双へと突入
Betting the guild and plunging into unmatched power
どちらもクリアが見えません
I can't see the clearing for either
アイコンタクト異常なし！アイテムはどこで買えますか？
Eye contact, no abnormalities! Where can I buy items?
偏差値、説明、足りないどこー？
Deviation value, explanation—where are they lacking?
ゆとりないの私のIMT
There's no room for my IMT
魔法のマンション超えてやるけど
I'll surpass the magic mansion, but...
その前に誰かいませんか？
...is there anyone there before that?
ちゃんと届いてるあなたのエール
Your cheers are reaching me clearly
意地・脱法・逆らい・絶対・不滅・大失敗もダイジェストの助走
Stubbornness, loopholes, defiance, absolute, immortal—even huge failures are just a run-up for the digest
ラヴィラヴィ小さなビットにでっかい愛をパーシンチュウ
Love-it, Love-it, 100% of my big love in a tiny bit
うまくいかないプレイング
Playing that doesn't go well
迷走だってあなたとしたい
I want to be lost even with you
私を見ててほしいの
I want you to look at me
よそ見はしないでね不器用でも愛してね
Don't look away, and love me even if I'm clumsy
まだ飛べるから
Because I can still fly
ラヴィラヴィまだまだあなたとでっかい愛をパーシンチュウ
Love-it, Love-it, still 100% of my big love with you
暴走しちゃったら静止してね
If I go out of control, please stop me
だって愛は必勝主義
Because love is a must-win principle
もっともっと跳ねてたいからずっとそばで見守って
I want to bounce more and more, so please keep watching over me from nearby
いってきますねー！
I'm off then!
どんなものでもくださいな
Give me anything you've got
月まで届くランデブー
A rendezvous that reaches the moon
ラララララララビー
La la la la la la la-by
もっとしたいの ララララララビー
I want to do more, la la la la la la-by
ラビー！
Laby!
祈りなさい
Offer your prayers
願いなさい
Make your wishes
有明アリーナのあんたたちのために
For all of you here at Ariake Arena
今、最強女神、兎田ぺこらが
Now, the strongest goddess, Usada Pekora...
舞い降りる！
...descends!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
疲れきってしぼんだあんたの
When you're all worn out and withered...
最強！
Strongest!
救けよと声 女神降臨！
A voice calls for help, and the goddess descends!
実況！！
Live commentary!!
待たせなさい どこに起こる
Make them wait, no matter where it happens
今日も明日も 浦安谷に
Today or tomorrow, in Urayasu Valley...
ペコペコしてる？ もっと！
...are you going "Peko peko"? More!
崇めるぺこ？ いいっすね！
Worshipping me? I like it!
全知全能 兎田ご奉仕
Omniscient and omnipotent, Usada at your service
まだまだ全然 極まりません！
I'm still far from reaching my peak!
崇めなさい ごっつぁんです！
Worship me! Thank you for the support!
ドンドンバババダンダン！
Don don ba ba ba dan dan!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
兎田の花 咲かせましょう
Let the flowers of Usada bloom
世界一のごもっとも
The most reasonable thing in the world
兎田ぺこら 参ります！
Usada Pekora, here I come!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
兎田の意地 見せましょうば
Let's show the pride of Usada
どんちゃん騒ぎ パリラリラ
A big ruckus, pari rari ra
あんたもあんたもあんたたちもみんな！
You, and you, and all of you too!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
ぺこらの配信は？
How is Pekora's stream?
ぺこらの実況は？
How is Pekora's commentary?
ぺこらの言うことは？
What does Pekora say?
兎耳立てて神バレろ！
Perk up those rabbit ears and reveal the god!
満点！
Full marks!
あんたたち！ やるぺこじゃん！
You guys! Not bad at all, peko!
最強！
Strongest!
ぺこらぺこら ありがとう！
Pekora, Pekora, thank you!
もっと！ もっと！ 大きな声で！
More! More! With a louder voice!
ぺこらぺこら ありがとう！
Pekora, Pekora, thank you!
最終鬼畜 兎田教官
The ultimate brutal instructor, Usada
今でも十分 可愛いだろ！
I'm plenty cute already, right?!
ぺこらぺこら ありがとう！
Pekora, Pekora, thank you!
崇めなさい ごっつぁんです！
Worship me! Thank you for the support!
ドンドンバババダンダン！
Don don ba ba ba dan dan!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
兎田の魂 沈めましょう
Let's appease the soul of Usada
宇宙一のごもっとも
The most reasonable thing in the universe
兎田ぺこら 大勝利！
Usada Pekora, a huge victory!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
兎田の導き 極めましょう
Let's master the guidance of Usada
うさぎと女神 開幕だ！
The rabbit and the goddess, the show is starting!
あんたもあんたもあんたたちもみんな！
You, and you, and all of you too!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
最強！
Strongest!
最強女神 兎田ぺこら！
The strongest goddess, Usada Pekora!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
あんたの合図で
At your signal
最高まで
Until the very best
ちゅ！
Chu!
出会えるなんて 嬉しいね
I'm so happy to be able to meet you
待ち遠しくて足をバタバタしながら
Kicking my legs in anticipation...
今日楽しみで
...I've been looking forward to today
寝れなかったよ
I couldn't even sleep!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous!
一秒も無駄にできない
I can't waste a single second
さぁ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin
君も
You too
せーの いらっしゃいませ！
One, two... Welcome!
好きが集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where love gathers
非日常はスナックの中
The extraordinary is inside the snack bar
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損損
If you came here, you've gotta dance or you're missing out
ピー・イー・ケー・オー・ラ 今は関係ない
P-E-K-O-R-A, it doesn't matter right now
態度の大小とか気にしない
I don't care about the size of your attitude
ちゃんと見えてる
I can clearly see
君のサイリウム
your light sticks
今はふっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it's just a tiny talent
小さな小さな才能だけど
that could blow away with a puff,
また一歩を 見ててくれるのなら
But if you keep watching my next step,
どこまでも愛をあげる
I'll give you love without end
あなたのアイドル
Your idol,
サイコーはピー・イー
the best is P-E-
チュー！
Chu!
愛も願おう 立てたアンテナ
Let's pray for love, antenna up
自慢してほしいよ
I want you to be proud
かじってられない
Can't just be nibbling,
君と君とサンバ
Samba with you and you
ひきこもりも ひとりしきりも
Whether you're a shut-in or just keep to yourself
普段と違う顔見せてよ
Show me a face I don't usually see
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
Everyone's a sibling, how're you doing?
なりふり構わずに
Without a care for appearances
ピー・イー・ダブリュー・ダブリュー・ダブリュー 今は関係ない
P-E-W-W-W, it still doesn't matter
愛想の良し悪しとか気にしない
I don't care about your sociability
絶好調 強すぎて 君のサイリウム
In top form, too strong, your light sticks
たとえ世界が終わる時も 拒まない
Even if the world ends, I won't refuse
ひとりぼっちを感じた時も
Even when you feel all alone
あなたが味方でいてくれたら 怖いものはないよね
If you're on my side, there's nothing to fear
見てよ見てよ 何か始まる
Look, look, something's starting,
君との物語が
a story with you
なんて素晴らしい景色だ
What a wonderful view
ピー・イー・ケー・オー・ラ 今は関係ない
P-E-K-O-R-A, it doesn't matter right now
態度の大小とか気にしない
I don't care about the size of your attitude
ちゃんと見えてる 君のサイリウム
I can clearly see your light sticks
今はふっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it's just a tiny talent
小さな小さな才能だけど
that could blow away with a puff,
私を推してくれるのなら
If you'll support me,
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
If you're on my side,
怖くないよ
I'm not afraid
どこまでも愛をあげる
I'll give you love without end
あなたのアイドル
Your idol,
サイコーはピー・イー・チュー！
the best is P-E-Chu!
1st 兎田ぺこらいぶ「うさぎ the MEGAMI!!」に
For coming to the 1st Usada Pekolive
来てくれて、ありぺこみーなー！
'Usagi the MEGAMI!!', thank you all!
あんたたちの声、めちゃめちゃ聞こえたよー！
I could hear your voices so well!
もう会場地響き鳴ってたぐらいに凄かった！
It was so amazing, the venue was
本当にありがとう！嬉しいよー！
practically shaking! Thank you! I'm so happy!
いや本当に広いよー！やっほー！見えてるよー！おー！見えてるよー！
Wow, it's really huge! Yahoo! I see you! Oh! I see you!
こっちも行っちゃおっかな？おー！見えてるよー！おー！見えてるよー！
Maybe I'll go over here too? Oh! I see you! Oh! I see you!
広っ！おー！本当だ凄い！うわー！
It's so big! Oh, you're right, amazing! Whoa!
ということでついに始まりました！みんな！兎田ぺこらソロライブ！
And so, it's finally begun! Everyone! Usada Pekora's solo live!
気持ちはみんな、どうですかー！？
How is everyone feeling!?
ぺこらもね、初っ端からみんなにボルテージガッて上げてもらって、
Pekora's voltage was cranked way up by all of you from the very start,
ぺこらも気持ちもう、やばぺこなんですけども！
And I'm feeling totally 'yaba-peko'!
うわ、なんか... やばい！ みんなやばいよ！ みんな、どうしよう。始まっちゃった、始まっちゃった！
Whoa, it's... crazy! Everyone, this is crazy! Everyone, what should I do? It's started, it's started!
落ち着け。まだまだ何曲もある。落ち着け、ぺこらだぞ。
Calm down. There are still many songs left. Calm down, it's me, Pekora.
そしてね、今回のライブのハッシュタグ「#うさめがぺこら」で、たくさんたくさんのポストして頂けたら嬉しいなと思いますので...
And, regarding the hashtag for this live concert, "#UsamegaPekora"... I'd be happy if you could post lots and lots with it...
トレンド入り、よろしぺこだよ！ お願いぺこー！
Let's get it trending, please-Peko! Pretty please-Peko!
いや、すごい。いや、マジでやばい。あんたたち、やばくない？ え、やば！
Whoa, incredible. No, seriously, this is crazy. Aren't you guys amazing? Whoa, crazy!
マジで、本当にやばい！
Seriously, truly crazy!
なんかもう、あんたたちに今からさ、ぺこらのこのソロライブの、ちょっとまぁ楽しみ方と言いますか、ちょっと説明しようかなと思ったんだけど...
I was thinking of explaining to you all now how to, well, enjoy my solo live concert, but...
あんたたちなんかもう十分、なんか出来てそうだけど一応伝えるね。
You guys seem like you're doing well enough already, but I'll tell you just in case.
一応、みんなペンライト持ってる？ 持ってるよね？ 持ってますよねー？ ああ、持ってる持ってる、持ってる持ってる...
Just in case, does everyone have their penlights? You do, right? You have them, right? Oh, I see them, I see them...
ペンライトね、色とかが何色かあると思います。
For the penlights, I think there are several colors available.
で、曲によって「え、これ何の曲だろう？ 何の色にしようかな？」っていう風にね、思う方もいると思うぺこなんですが...
And depending on the song, I'm sure some of you might be wondering, "Wait, what song is this? Which color should I use?"...
あれ、今、映ってる？ ここさ、両端にさ、こっちと...
Oh, is it showing now? On both ends here, this side and...
ちょっと待って。ごめんね、はあ、はあ、はあ...
Wait a second. Sorry, *panting*...
こっち側にね、デッカいスクリーンあったと思うぺこら。ぺこらが等身大映ってて、野うさぎたちがペンライト持ってるやつがあると思うんですけど...
On this side, I think there was a huge screen, Peko. One where I'm shown full-size and the Nousagi are holding penlights...
そのね、野うさぎが持ってるペンライトの色に、あの、合わせてもらえたら、あの... いいかな、迷ってる人はね。
If you could match the color of the penlights those Nousagi are holding... that would be good, for those who are unsure.
「いや、僕、私、迷ってません！ この色でずっとやっていきます！」っていう人だったら、もうそれでも全然いいぺこなんですが...
But if you're like, "No, I'm not unsure! I'm sticking with this color the whole time!", then that's totally fine Peko too...
もしね、ペンライト迷ってる人がいたら、あちらもあるのでよろしくお願いします。
If anyone is unsure about the penlight color, please refer to that too.
そして！ いや、あんたたちのコール、マジで最高だって！ ほんと、もう、ずしーんって脳みそにも来たぺこなんですけども...
And! Man, your calls are seriously the best! Truly, they really hit me right in the brain, Peko...
この上！ ぺこらの頭上、ぴょん！
Above here! Above my head, boing!
この上にね、あの表示されている歌詞だったり、言葉、コールとかはね、もしね知っていれば一緒に歌ってもほしいしコールもしてほしいので...
Up here, if you know the lyrics, words, or calls being displayed... I want you to sing along and do the calls with me...
上もちょっとチラチラ見ながら... ま、でも、ぺこらのことずっと見ててね。
So please keep an eye on that too... but keep your eyes on me the whole time, okay?
基本的には、そうだよあんたたち。わかってるよね？
Basically, that's right you guys. You understand, right?
見るのはぺこらだからね！ ま、ちょ、チラチラは見ていいけど、基本的にはもうぺこらしか視界に入れちゃダメだからね。いいぺこ？
The one you're watching is me! Well, you can take a peek, but basically, you shouldn't have anyone but me in your sight. Got it, Peko?
あー、いいなー。なんか気持ちいいな、今日。なんか、すごい気持ちいいな。
Ah, this is great. It feels so good today. It feels really, really good.
なんか、今日歌うのやめてこのまま話そうか、みんなと。どう？
I kind of feel like stopping the singing today and just chatting like this with everyone. What do you think?
え、なに、どっちの反応それ？ ちょっと、え、どっち、え、どっちの反応？
Wait, what kind of reaction is that? Wait, which one, which reaction?
え、「いい」ってこと？ 「いい」ってこと？ え、「いい」ってこと？ こっちの人たち。
Wait, you mean "it's okay"? You mean "it's okay"? You mean "it's okay", you people over here?
おおー、おおー... なんか分かりづれーな、反応的に。
Ooh, ooh... Your reaction is a bit hard to read.
どうしようかな、歌うのやめようかな今日。話す？ なんかもう、30時間くらい兎田ぺこらと雑談ソロライブにしとく？
What should I do? Should I stop singing today? Talk? Should we just make this a 30-hour chatting solo live with Usada Pekora?
いや、いいか！ いやいや、ダメぺこでしょう！ あんたたち、ぺこらの歌を聴きに来たぺこなんでしょう？
Wait, never mind! No, no, that's no good, Peko! You guys came to hear my songs, didn't you?
ああ、よかったわ。反応なかったらどうしようかなとか思っちゃったぺこだけど。
Phew, thank goodness. I was worried about what I'd do if there was no reaction, Peko.
いや、でも、なんか本当に夢みたいぺこだな。ぺこらがこのソロライブで...
But, wow, it really feels like a dream, Peko. Me, having this solo live...
あんたたちのおかげだね、本当にありがとうね。
It's all thanks to you all. Truly, thank you so much.
なんかぺこらも緊張してる、まだ。あー、緊張してるけど、最後までみんながね、楽しんでいってくれたらぺこらも本当に嬉しいぺこなんで...
I'm still nervous too. Ah, I'm nervous, but if everyone enjoys it until the end, I'll be really happy, Peko...
よろぺこです！
Count on me, Peko!
そして、YouTubeとTikTokで今ご覧になられている方がいると思うんですけども...
And, I believe there are people watching right now on YouTube and TikTok...
その無料チラ見せがなんと、ここまで、ということで。
but this free sneak peek ends here.
「えー、ヤダ！ ヤダヤダ！ 見たい見たい！」って言う人や、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい人は...
"Eeeh, no way! No, no! I want to watch, I want to watch!" For those who say that, and those who want to keep getting hyped together...
ぜひとも概要欄から配信サイトへ行ってもらって、最後までぺこらにコールや応援をしてくれたらめちゃくちゃ嬉しいので...
Please go to the streaming site from the description section. I'd be so happy if you could keep doing calls and supporting me until the end...
よろぺこです！ それでは皆さん、おっふー！
Count on me, Peko! Now then, everyone... Off-fhoo!
きれいな水色だね、本当に。よし。
It's a beautiful light blue, truly. Alright.
それでは、いよいよと「全人類兎化計画」のフィナーレへと行っておこうかなと思います。
And now, I think it's finally time to head toward the finale of the "Whole Humanity Rabbitification Plan".
ついにフィナーレとなるので、皆さんも心して聴いて頂けたらなと思います。
It's finally the finale, so I hope you all listen with your whole hearts.
それでは！ みんなで「全人類兎化計画」を成功させるぺこー！
Now then! Let's make the "Whole Humanity Rabbitification Plan" a success together, Peko!
無料パートは終了いたしました / ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion of the stream has ended. / Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended.
Thank you for watching!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うーさぎ！うーさぎ！
U-sagi! U-sagi!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ぺーこら！ぺーこら！
Pe-kora! Pe-kora!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ぺーこら！ぺーこら！
Pe-kora! Pe-kora!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うーさぎ！
U-sagi!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!